or David David
m in your work as an accountant What do you do
for type of
check You can probably specify it
depends a bit on which type of
in this
the case Yes, I do several different ones
cash cash in that sense
to be made transfers from
bank accounts for example Then it's new
information that needs to be taken into account
absolutely always if there is a new one
information, you need to make a new one
assessment in the case regarding the risk then
somewhere uh it's out of bounds
I'm sitting in Karlstad, isn't it
impossible that you have Norwegian customers who
as speculators on their objects in the south
Sweden Could it be that you target yourself
more towards Denmark then that you have eh Danish
German customers who want to buy real estate in